http://www.deskpicture.com/privacypolicy.html

DeskPicture.com - Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
DeskPicture.com
Privacy Policy
This privacy statement is intended to give you, the user of this website, an awareness about what information this website collects, how this information is used, and how this affects your privacy while using this site.
Behavioral Advertising Policy
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.
Third Party Advertising
We use BUDS INC and other third-party advertising companies to
serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use
information (not including your name, address, email address or
telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in
order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about
goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would
like more information about this practice and to know your choices
about not having this information used by these companies, please
click here
Logging and Statistics
When a user views a page, image or other item on this site, the user's IP address, browser type, and the site you came from is stored in a log file. None of this information can be used to personally identify an individual user. The details stored in this log file may be used to provide statistics about the usage of this site, for the purpose of improving the site and to provide statistical information to advertisers. Only aggregated information is given, and the log file itself is not available to the public.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party
advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. These cookies are not sent from our
site and we have no access to the information in these cookies.
It is possible for users to reject cookies. This is a feature of the user's browser. It is possible to use this site without cookies.
The information in cookies on this site is in no way able to track the user's actions or
behavior, or gain demographic information on the user.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that
we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other
sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site
and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that
collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement
applies solely to information collected by this Web site. .
© 2011 Meyer Media LLC
Send feedback to webmaster@deskpicture.com
View our Privacy Policy
